http://bob-baker.com/buzz/privacy-policy/

Contact
Privacy Policy / Cookies / GDPR / Etc.
Hi. Bob here. I care about the your personal information, so I’m using this page to give you some basic info on the privacy practices used at TheBuzzFactor.com, FullTimeAuthor.com, PromoteYourCreativity.com, and Bob-Baker.com.
Certain areas of the world now require different privacy disclosures, so please read this to make sure you understand my practices.
What Personal Data Is Collected From You?
Personal data is information that can be used to identify you, such as your name, IP address, and email address. As a business, I collect personal data from you in a number of ways, including:
When You Opt In to One of My Email Lists: Your name and email address.
When You Purchase Something from This Website: Your name, email address, billing information, and payment source.
What Is the Purpose of Processing Your Personal Data?
I collect the information above for the following purposes:
To deliver email updates on topics, tips and tools you have opted into and expressed an interested in.
To process a purchase you make directly from one of my websites.
Who Has Access to the Data Collected?
I use third party services to assist with processing your personal data, including:
Financial transaction processors (such as PayPal, Gumroad, etc.)
Email management service (such as Aweber)
For purchases and financial transactions, I have access to your name, address, and email via the third party service. But I do NOT have access to your credit card or banking info. That is used securely by the service.
For email lists, your data is held in the online database of the email management service. I periodically download the database to my local hard drive as a backup.
I NEVER sell, rent, or give away your data to anyone.
How Long Is Your Data Kept?
I keep your personal data for different periods of time depending on the reason it was gathered.
Opt-In Emails: Indefinitely until you unsubscribe
Transactions: Four years for tax audit purposes
Cookies and Embedded Content from Other Websites
I don’t use or collect cookies on this website. However …
Pages on my websites may include embedded content (videos, images, articles, etc.), such as YouTube videos and SoundCloud audio players. Embedded content from other websites often behaves in the same way as if the visitor is on the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Your Right to Ask for Corrections, Erasure, and Export of Your Data
You have the following rights: The right to be informed about my privacy policy, to access the data I have about you, to request I update any incorrect data, and to request I erase certain data about you. You also have the right to ask me to restrict certain types of processing of your information and to object to how I use your data.
To exercise any of these rights, please send an email to bob@bob-baker.com with your request.
Contact information
PO Box 28441
St. Louis, MO 63146
(314) 329-1395
THANKS!
Share this:FacebookTwitterLinkedInPinterestMorePrintRedditPocketTumblr
Attract More Fans, Sell More Music, Get More Exposure!
Click here to get it now ...
Connect with Bob …
Search for:
Top Music Resources
Recent Posts
Build Your Fanbase! 5 Ways to Thank Your Fans
The No 1 Music Marketing Question to Ask Yourself
30-Day Challenge! Master Your Mindset!
Lessons from Simon Tam and the CD Baby Music Conference
Ralph Murphy Tribute: The Songwriter’s Secret Weapon
Turning Pro: Get Your ASK Out There!
Get Paid What You’re Worth as a Musician
Most Popular Posts
Niche Music Markets: 7 Great Examples
How to Promote a New Album: 25 Artists and Marketing Experts Give Their Best Advice
[New Book] The Passion Principles
Sum Yourself Up in One Sentence
Indie Musician Defined: What Does “Indie” Mean?
